[Music]
my oh my what a wonderful looking
gingerbread house
I sure hope nobody minds if I have a
little snack I know I shouldn't but this
house tastes just so darn good I can't
help myself
hey there what are you doing taking
bites out of my chimney
oh this was your house I'm so sorry I
was just so hungry that's all right my
newfound friend the peppermint root up
is indeed rather beautiful much like
those two cute cap drops on your
backside
tee hee hee oh you my gumdrops aren't
that bad well I have to disagree with
you when I look at them I want nothing
more than to smother my face between
those cheeks oh stop you're making me
blush I can do more than that how about
you come inside so we can get to know
each other better it would be my
pleasure
[Music]
God oh my God
I just broke my leg God it hurts so bad
Bart levy you have to do something maybe
if you poop on me you're icing might be
sticky enough to reattach my leg I'm Way
ahead of you [ __ ] I hope you like
strawberry Bart levy you that you saved
my life now I can walk again huh hey
[ __ ] why are you flying away get back
down here before you hurt yourself
you